(Sheldon:)Muggles.
(Raj:)You slipped and fell
into a robot hand?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Raj:)Penis first?
(Howard:)Yes. Now, help me!
(Leonard:)I'd suggest a lubricant,
but I have a feeling
(Leonard:)you fell on some
of that as well.
(Howard:)Not funny, Leonard.
(Raj:)Really? A robot hand's got
a death grip on your junk, dude.
(Raj:)That's funny, ask anyone.
Plea-- before my mother
walks in, get this off me!
(Leonard:)Okay, let's see.
(Howard:)No, no!
Don't touch.
(Howard:)The program
is paused.
(Leonard:)Well, then let's
un-pause it.
(Howard:)No, no! I loaded
the wrong program.
(Howard:)The hand thinks it's holding
a screwdriver in outer space.
(Howard:)If you continue the program,
it's gonna start twisting.
(Raj:)A-All right.
(Raj:)Um, how about this.
When-when Winnie the Pooh
got his head stuck
(Raj:)in the honey tree,
his friends all grabbed onto him